About Me

Graduated IT Engineer Assistant with good knowledge of IT technology. Currently working as a System Administrator at Genesis.

As an experienced IT system administrator with 4 years of experience in managing and maintaining complex IT infrastructures, I am dedicated to providing reliable and secure technology solutions to organizations. My strong technical skills, attention to detail, and problem-solving abilities make me an effective team player in achieving IT goals.

I also have 2.5 years of experience in a remarkably busy retail environment as a diligent and customer focused support technician. I have great technical knowledge in Microsoft technologies, POS and desktop support and remarkable customer service manner.

Experience

Genesis

System Administrator - MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Managing and maintaining the company's IT infrastructure in UK, Brazil, and the US, including servers, network devices, and software applications
- Providing worldwide support to users in UK, Brazil and the US and resolving system-related issues in a timely manner
- Implementing security best practices and technologies to protect against cyber threats and data breaches in all locations
- Designed and implemented backup and disaster recovery strategies to ensure business continuity in all locations
- Conducting regular system updates, patches, and upgrades to ensure optimal performance and security in all locations
- Collaborating with other IT team members worldwide to plan and implement IT projects and initiatives
- Implementing Azure AD and SSO for multiple applications, improving security and simplifying user access
- Provisioning and managing Azure VMs for various workloads, including SQL Server and web applications
- Administering Microsoft Intune for Windows and MAC device management and application deployment, improving user productivity and security
- Administering VOIP phone systems to ensure optimal performance and reliability

Caffe Nero

Infrastructure Engineer - APRIL 2021 - MARCH 2022

- First technical point of contact for the Head Office with over 300 users. Assisting users with their desktop

support issues (Windows, AD, networking, printing, hardware and software support, PC and mobile, conferencing software and hardware, VPN, IP phones)

- Upkeep of office's IT infrastructure
- Ownership of IMAC process
- Provisioning of new PCs (Windows/MacOs, both laptop and desktop) and mobiles (iOS and Android)
- Managing, supporting, and troubleshooting mobiles (Meraki MDM, BT OnePhone)
- Setting up and training new starters
- Reporting to Service Manager
- Creating Knowledge Base entries
- Escalating issues with 3rd line colleagues

Caffe Nero

Support Analyst - MARCH 2019- APRIL 2021

- First technical point of contact for 900+ Caffe Nero stores (including international sites)
- Resolving technical issues (EPOS, PDQs, PCs, printing, small networks)
- Logging and updating tickets in internal ticketing software
- Provisioning and fixing hardware including laptops, desktops and mobiles
- Assisting with IT department projects
- Administration of store facing systems like intranet and ordering system

Skills

POS and Desktop Support

Windows 7, 10

Active Directory

Provisioning new computers, mobile devices

AV setup for conferencing (Zoom based)

Installation and operation of applications

Hardware installation, configuration and operation

Installation and operation of technical information systems

Cisco CCNA basic knowledge (old certificate from the Engineer assistant degree)

Microsoft Office + Office 365

Okta SSO

Meraki MDM

Active directory

Active directory and Azure AD

System administration of Windows servers and desktops

Virtualization technologies

Network administration and troubleshooting

Security best practices and technologies

Backup and disaster recovery strategies

Cloud computing platforms such as Azure (and basic AWS)

Azure VM provisioning and management

Microsoft Intune administration

Phone system administration (VOIP – Teams and Zoom)

Onboarding and offboarding process for new starters

Education

II. Ferenc Rákóczi School, - Engineering Assistant – Technical Informatics University of Pécs, - IT Engineer (Half finished)

2009-2011 2012-2014

Languages

Hungarian - Native English - full professional proficiency

Hobbies and interests

Football

Certificated football referee in Hungary (2005-2014)